(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(t,e,c){},11:function(t,e,c){"use strict";c.r(e);var r=c(1),n=c(4),s=c.n(n),o=c(2),i=c(0);var a=function(t){var e=t.questionNum,c=t.data,n=t.setStop,s=t.setQuestionNum,a=Object(r.useState)(null),u=Object(o.a)(a,2),d=u[0],x=u[1],j=Object(r.useState)(null),l=Object(o.a)(j,2),m=l[0],b=l[1],O=Object(r.useState)(""),f=Object(o.a)(O,2),v=f[0],h=f[1];Object(r.useEffect)((function(){x(c[e+Math.floor(9*Math.random())])}),[c,e]);var p=function(t,e){setTimeout((function(){e()}),t)};return Object(i.jsxs)("div",{className:"quest",children:[Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"main-que",children:null===d||void 0===d?void 0:d.question}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"awnser",children:null===d||void 0===d?void 0:d.answers.map((function(t,e){return Object(i.jsx)("span",{className:m===t?v:"",onClick:function(){return function(t){b(t),h("active"),p(3e3,(function(){h(t.correct?"correct":"wrong")})),p(6e3,(function(){!0===t.correct?(s((function(t){return t+1})),b(null)):n(!0)}))}(t)},children:t.text},e)}))})]})},u=[{id:1,question:"\u0645\u0646 \u0647\u0648 \u0627\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0644\u0641\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u0631\u0627\u0634\u062f\u064a\u0646",answers:[{text:"\u0639\u0645\u0631 \u0628\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u0637\u0627\u0628",correct:!1},{text:"\u0639\u0644\u064a \u0628\u0646 \u0627\u0628\u064a \u0637\u0627\u0644\u0628",correct:!1},{text:"\u0627\u0628\u0648 \u0628\u0643\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062f\u064a\u0642",correct:!0},{text:"\u0639\u062b\u0645\u0627\u0646 \u0628\u0646 \u0639\u0641\u0627\u0646",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:"\u0639\u062f\u062f \u0639\u062c\u0627\u0626\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u062f\u0646\u064a\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0633\u0628\u0639",answers:[{text:"5",correct:!1},{text:"7",correct:!0},{text:"9",correct:!1},{text:"4",correct:!1}]},{id:3,question:"\u0645\u062a\u064a \u0627\u0646\u062a\u0647\u062a \u0627\u0644\u062d\u0631\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u062b\u0627\u0646\u064a\u0629",answers:[{text:"1940",correct:!1},{text:"1945",correct:!0},{text:"1939",correct:!1},{text:"1938",correct:!1}]},{id:4,question:"\u0627\u0648\u0644 \u063a\u0632\u0648\u0629 \u0641\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645",answers:[{text:"\u0628\u062f\u0631",correct:!0},{text:"\u0627\u062d\u062f",correct:!1},{text:"\u0627\u0644\u062e\u0646\u062f\u0642",correct:!1},{text:"\u0645\u0624\u062a\u0629",correct:!1}]},{id:5,question:"\u0639\u062f\u062f \u0633\u0648\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0642\u0631\u0627\u0621\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0631\u064a\u0645",answers:[{text:"108",correct:!1},{text:"110",correct:!1},{text:"120",correct:!1},{text:"114",correct:!0}]},{id:6,question:"\u0627\u062e\u0631 \u0645\u0644\u0643 \u062a\u0648\u0644\u064a \u062d\u0643\u0645 \u0645\u0635\u0631",answers:[{text:"\u0641\u0624\u0627\u062f",correct:!1},{text:"\u0641\u0627\u0631\u0648\u0642",correct:!0},{text:"\u0627\u0633\u0645\u0627\u0639\u064a\u0644",correct:!1},{text:"\u0645\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0646\u062c\u064a\u0628",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"\u0639\u062f\u062f \u0627\u062d\u062c\u0627\u0631 \u0627\u0644\u0647\u0631\u0645 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0643\u0628\u0631",answers:[{text:"10000000",correct:!1},{text:"1000000",correct:!1},{text:"\u0645\u0634 \u0639\u0627\u0631\u0641",correct:!0},{text:"\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0630\u0644\u0643",correct:!1}]},{id:8,question:"\u0644\u0627\u0639\u0628 \u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a \u062d\u0635\u0644 \u0639\u0644\u064a \u062f\u0648\u0631\u064a \u0627\u0628\u0637\u0627\u0644 \u0627\u0648\u0631\u0628\u0627 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062f\u0648\u0631\u064a \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0646\u062c\u0644\u064a\u0632\u064a",answers:[{text:"\u0645\u062d\u0645\u062f \u0635\u0644\u0627\u062d",correct:!0},{text:"\u0631\u0627\u0628\u062d \u0645\u062c\u0631",correct:!1},{text:"\u0627\u0634\u0631\u0641 \u062d\u0643\u064a\u0645\u064a",correct:!1},{text:"\u062e\u0627\u0633\u0631 \u0645\u062c\u0631",correct:!1}]},{id:9,question:"\u0639\u062f\u062f \u0627\u0631\u0643\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0633\u0644\u0627\u0645",answers:[{text:"3",correct:!1},{text:"4",correct:!1},{text:"6",correct:!1},{text:"5",correct:!0}]},{id:10,question:" \u0627\u0643\u0645\u0644 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u062b\u0644 \u0631\u0628 \u0627\u062e\u0627 \u0644\u0645 \u062a\u0644\u062f\u0647",answers:[{text:"\u0627\u0645\u0643",correct:!0},{text:"\u0627\u062e\u062a\u0643",correct:!1},{text:"\u0627\u0628\u0646 \u062e\u0627\u0644\u062a\u0643 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u064a \u0627\u0645\u0643 \u0628\u062a\u0642\u0648\u0644 \u0627\u062d\u0633\u0646 \u0645\u0646\u0643",correct:!1},{text:"\u0639\u0645\u062a\u0643",correct:!1}]}],d=[{id:10,money:"$ 1000000"},{id:9,money:"$ 700000"},{id:8,money:"$ 500000"},{id:7,money:"$ 100000"},{id:6,money:"$ 50000"},{id:5,money:"$ 10000"},{id:4,money:"$ 5000"},{id:3,money:"$ 1000"},{id:2,money:"$ 500"},{id:1,money:"$ 100"}];function x(t){var e=t.questionNum,c=t.setStop,n=Object(r.useState)(30),s=Object(o.a)(n,2),i=s[0],a=s[1];return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){0===i&&c(!0);var t=setInterval((function(){a((function(t){return t-1}))}),1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(t)}}),[c,i]),Object(r.useEffect)((function(){a(30)}),[e]),i}c(10);var j=function(){var t=Object(r.useState)(1),e=Object(o.a)(t,2),c=e[0],n=e[1],s=Object(r.useState)(!1),j=Object(o.a)(s,2),l=j[0],m=j[1];return Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:l?Object(i.jsx)("h1",{className:"endGAme",children:"game over you earned: $0"}):Object(i.jsxs)(i.Fragment,{children:[Object(i.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"top",children:Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"timer",children:Object(i.jsx)(x,{setStop:m,questionNum:c})})}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"bottom",children:Object(i.jsx)(a,{data:u,questionNum:c,setStop:m,setQuestionNum:n})})]}),Object(i.jsx)("div",{className:"pyramid",children:Object(i.jsx)("ul",{className:"money-list",children:d.map((function(t){return Object(i.jsxs)("li",{className:c===t.id?"listItem active":"listItem",children:[Object(i.jsx)("span",{className:"quenum",children:t.id}),Object(i.jsx)("span",{children:t.money})]},t.id)}))})})]})})};s.a.render(Object(i.jsx)(j,{}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.a41bf40c.chunk.js.map